Guide to the Kristine Stiles Collection, 1900-[ongoing] RL.01254
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Artist Archive, 101 boxes
  - Kaprow, Allan (USA) (Box 61)
    - Correspondence (Box 61)
    - Gallery catalogs (Box 61)
    - Journal (Box 61)
    - Audiocassette of taped interview (Box 61)
    - Sweet Walls and Testimonials (Box 61)
  - Katz, Rebecca (Box 62)
    - Correspondence (Box 62)
    - Photographs (Box 62)
    - Exhibition program (Box 62)
    - CD with pictures of artwork (Box 62)
  - Katzenstein, Uri (Israel) (Box 63)
    - Stiles' correspondence with others about his art, 2000s (Box 63)
    - Slides (Box 63)
    - Catalogs (Box 63)
    - Napkin (relic of performance at Duke University), 2000 (Box 63)
    - 3 microcassettes of taped interviews (Box 63)
  - Knizak, Milan (Czechoslovakia, b. 1942) (Box 64)
    - Correspondence and notes, 1980s-1990s (Box 64)
    - DIAS relationship materials (Box 64)
    - 2 cassettes, 1996 (Box 64)
    - Postcards and photographs of artwork (Box 64)
    - Milan Knizak, work of art: Aktual bag (bag made with camouflage material) (Box 191)
    - Milan Knizak, work of art: Nicolai Ostrovskij, Jan Se Kalila Ocel, 1952 (book with bullet holes, A Target written over book jacket) (Box 191)
    - Milan Knizak, work of art: Gorkij, Po Svazu Sovetu, 1952 (book burned) (Box 191)
    - Milan Knizak, work of art: About Destruction, circa 1966 (torn hand-written, hand-painted manuscript) (Box 191)
    - Milan Knizak, work of art: Millions of Anonymous Messiahs are Necessary, includes items as early as 1965 (Box 191)
      Torn, handwritten, mimeographed, and typed samizdat book with paintings and manifestos. Also includes envelope with Czech stamps to Ralphael Montanez Ortiz for DIAS-USA, 1968. Stiles acquired this object when Ortiz gave her his archive around 1985.
  - Knowles, Alison (USA) (Box 65)
    - Artworks by Alison Knowles (2 copies) (Box 65)
    - Correspondence, notes, schedules, and gallery show advertisements, 1990s-2000s (Box 65)
    - 1 cassette tape (Box 65)
  - Kosuth, Joseph (Box 65)
    - Correspondence (Box 65)
    - Gallery advertisements (Box 65)
    - Two Oxford Reading Rooms (2 copies) (Box 65)
  - Latham, John (England) (Box 66)
    - Correspondence (Box 66)
    - 4 cassettes of taped interviews (Box 66)
    - Original artwork (Box 66)
    - Notes (Box 66)
    - Gallery catalogs and exhibition information (Box 66)
  - Lebel, Jean-Jacques (France) (Box 67-70)
    - Correspondence, 1980s-2000s, including the first letter from him to Stiles as well as many original collages and drawings on the letters (Box 67-70)
    - Maurice Hontang book: Psychologie du Che Val (Box 67-70)
    - 8 cassettes of taped interviews, 1980s, Paris
      - Tape 1 (Box 67, Audio-cassette RL01254-CS-0001, Digital-materials RL01254-SET-0002, Audio-file RL01254-CS-0001_01.wav, Audio-file RL01254-CS-0001_02.wav)
      - Tape 2 (Box 67, Audio-cassette RL01254-CS-0002, Digital-materials RL01254-SET-0002, Audio-file RL01254-CS-0002.wav)
      - Tape 3 (Box 67, Audio-cassette RL01254-CS-0003, Digital-materials RL01254-SET-0002, Audio-file RL01254-CS-0003_01.wav, Audio-file RL01254-CS-0003_02.wav)
      - Tape 4 (Box 67, Audio-cassette RL01254-CS-0004, Digital-materials RL01254-SET-0002, Audio-file RL01254-CS-0004.wav)
      - Tape 5 (Box 67, Audio-cassette RL01254-CS-0005, Digital-materials RL01254-SET-0002, Audio-file RL01254-CS-0005_01.wav, Audio-file RL01254-CS-0005_02.wav)
      - Tape 6 (Box 67, Audio-cassette RL01254-CS-0006, Digital-materials RL01254-SET-0002, Audio-file RL01254-CS-0006_01.wav, Audio-file RL01254-CS-0006_02.wav)
      - Tape 7 (Box 67, Audio-cassette RL01254-CS-0007, Digital-materials RL01254-SET-0002, Audio-file RL01254-CS-0007.wav)
      - Tape 8 (Box 67, Audio-cassette RL01254-CS-0008)
    - 3 microcassettes of taped interviews, 1998, Barcelona
      - Tape 1 (Box 67, Audio-cassette RL01254-MCS-0001, Digital-materials RL01254-SET-0002, Audio-file RL01254-MCS-0001.wav)
      - Tape 2 (Box 67, Audio-cassette RL01254-MCS-0002, Digital-materials RL01254-SET-0002, Audio-file RL01254-MCS-0002.wav)
      - Tape 3 (Box 67, Audio-cassette RL01254-MCS-0003, Digital-materials RL01254-SET-0002, Audio-file RL01254-MCS-0003.wav)
    - Slides, 1980s (Box 67-70)
    - Flyers and brochures for exhibitions (Box 67-70)
    - Press and articles about Lebel (Box 67-70)
    - Books by, about, or with essays by Lebel (Box 180 and 188)
      - Les Cahiers Noirs du Soleil 3 (no inscription) (Box 180 and 188)
      - Noir et Rouge 46, June 1970 (no inscription) (Box 180 and 188)
      - Grand Tableau Antifasciste Collectif exhibition catalogues, 2000 (2 copies: inscriptions in both books) (Box 180 and 188)
      - Philippe Dagen, Nos Femmes, exhibition catalogue, 2005 (inscription) (Box 180 and 188)
      - Jean-Jacques Lebel Soulevements, exhibition catalogues, 2009 (inscriptions in both books) (Box 180 and 188)
      - Jean-Jacques Lebel, L'amour et L'Argent, 1979 (inscription) (Box 180 and 188)
      - Happenings de Jean-Jacques Lebel ou l'insoumission radicale, 2009 (inscription) (Box 180 and 188)
      - Picasso L'Object du mythe, [date unknown] exhibition catalogue with essay by Lebel (inscription) (Box 180 and 188)
      - Polyphonix, exhbition catalogue, 2002 (2 copies: inscriptions in both books) (Box 180 and 188)
      - Deleuze, Un Album, exhibition catalogue, 2005 (inscription) (Box 180 and 188)
      - Jean-Jacques Lebel: Un tentative du montrage, exhibition catalogue, 2002 (inscription) (Box 180 and 188)
      - Antonin Artaud, exhibition catalogue, 2005, (inscription) (Box 180 and 188)
      - Now's the time: Photographies de Marcel Fleiss, text by Lebel, 2005 (inscription) (Box 180 and 188)
      - Jean Jacques Lebel: Reliquaire pur un culte de Vénus, exhibition catalogue, 2001 (inscription) (Box 180 and 188)
      - Jean-Jacques Lebel, exhibition catalogue, 2004 (2 copies: inscriptions in both books) (Box 180 and 188)
      - Jean-Jacques Lebel, exhibition catalogue, 1998 (inscription) (Box 180 and 188)
      - Erró, Fahlström, Köpcke, Lebel, 2003 (inscription) (Box 180 and 188)
      - Jean-Jacques Lebel, exhibition catalogue, 1991 (inscription) (Box 180 and 188)
      - Jean-Jacques Lebel, exhibition catalogue with essay by Kristine Stiles, 1999 (inscription) (Box 180 and 188)
      - La Fin d'un Millénaire, 2000 (inscription) (Box 180 and 188)
      - Jean-Jacques Lebel, pamphlet exhibition catalogue, 1990 (no inscription) (Box 180 and 188)
      - Francis Picabia, book with essay by Lebel, 2007 (inscription) (Box 180 and 188)
      - Poésie Directe, exhibition catalogue, 1990 (inscription + loose photograph) (Box 180 and 188)
      - Jean Jacques Lebel, exhibition catalogue, 1988 (inscription) (Box 180 and 188)
      - Jardín de eros, exhibition catalogue, 1999 (no inscription) (Box 180 and 188)
      - Change International deux, 1999, essay by Lebel (no inscription) (Box 180 and 188)
      - Poesie en Action, 2000 (no inscription) (Box 180 and 188)
      - Jean-Jacques Lebel, happenings, interventions et actions diverses, 1982 (inscription) (Box 180 and 188)
      - Chimeres n. 5/6, 1988; n. 7, 1988; and n. 6, 1989 (inscriptions in all) (Box 180 and 188)
      - Jean-Jacques Lebel Happening - Fluxus (no inscription) (Box 180 and 188)
      - 2005 agenda, 2005 (inscription) (Box 180 and 188)
      - Jean-Jacques Lebel, Rue Rossini, 1996 (inscription) (Box 180 and 188)
    - Jean-Jacques Lebel, Le Happening, 1966 (Stiles' photocopy from graduate school) (Box 180 and 188)
    - Jean-Jacques Lebel, Entretiens avec le Living Theater (Stiles' photocopy from graduate school) (Box 180 and 188)
    - Jean-Jacques Lebel, exhibition catalogue, 2003. Essay by Kristine Stiles (Box 180 and 188)
    - "Beat Generation: Kerouac/Ginsberg/Burroughs" film by Jean-Jacques Lebel and Xavier Villetard, dvd, 2013 (Box 67, Dvd RL01254-DVD-0001)
  - Lerager, James (USA) (Box 71)
    Photographer of the atomic and nuclear age, as well as Mexico's disappearing cultures, among other topics
    - Remembering Invisibility drafts by Stiles (Box 71)
    - Photocopies of Lerager's photographs (Box 71)
    - Correspondence (Box 71)
    - Gallery announcements and advertisements (Box 71)
    - Articles (Box 71)
    - CDs and photographs (Box 71)
  - Mailloux, Suzanne (USA, circa 1942) (Box 189)
    - Photographs from her wedding, circa 1980 (Box 189)
      Groom is Calogero Salvo (Venezuelan filmmaker); location is Roxy Theater, San Francisco. Stiles is a bridesmaid in green dress. Punk band Ramones conducted the ceremony.
  - Marioni, Tom (USA) (Box 176)
    - 4 audiocassettes of taped interviews, 1980s (Box 176)
    - Programs and press releases (Box 176)
    - Publications (Box 176)
    - Correspondence, 1989-1998 (Box 176)
  - Mathieu, Georges (France) (Box 57)
    - Correspondence about his art show in Paris and Stiles' scholarship and curating (Box 57)
    - Postcards and photocopies of paintings (Box 57)
    - Scholarly articles (Box 57)
  - McCarthy, Paul (USA) (Box 72)
    - Correspondence, notes, and articles, 1980s-1990s (Box 72)
    - Copies of interview transcripts, 1996 (Box 72)
    - Gallery advertisements and announcements (Box 72)
    - Slides and photographs (Box 72)
    - 2 audiocassettes of taped interviews (Box 72)
    - 4 minicassettes (Box 72)
  - McCarty, Lisa (USA) (Box 213, Box 215)
  - McFadden, Jane (Box 57)
    - Correspondence, 1990s-2000s (Box 57)
  - Metzger, Gustav (Germany) (Box 73-78)
    Also includes materials from DIAS (Destruction in Art Symposium), London, 1966.
    - Notes from the DIAS trial (Box 73-78)
    - Correspondence and postcards (Box 73-78)
    - Cassette tapes, including interviews (Box 73-78)
    - Photographs and film (Box 73-78)
    - DIAS Preview Folder (Box 73-78)
    - Post-DIAS materials (Box 73-78)
    - Magazines and publications covering DIAS, 1967-1968 (Box 73-78)
    - Exhibition publications (Box 73-78)
  - Micheline, Jack (USA) (Box 79-83)
    Oversize materials have been removed to the Oversize Posters series. See Box 194 and 195.
    - Original writings, including poetry, prose, and plays (Box 79-83)
    - Drawings and artwork (Box 79-83)
    - Newspapers (Box 79-83)
    - Correspondence, frequently with drawings (Box 79-83)
    - Cassette tapes (Box 79-83)
    - Yellow Horn, 1975 (signed copy) (Box 189)
    - Poems of Dr. Innisfree, 1975 (signed copy) (Box 189)
    - Last House in America, 1976 (signed copy with painting in it) (Box 189)
  - Miller, Larry (USA) (Box 84, Box 215)
    - Correspondence (Box 84, Box 215)
    - Articles (Box 84)
    - Interview notes on Mom-Me show and Jim the Wonder Dog documentary (Box 84)
    - Gallery catalogs (Box 84)
    - Slides (Box 84)
    - 2 audiocassettes of taped interviews (Box 84)
  - Montano, Linda (USA) (Box 86)
    - Correspondence, 2008-2009 (Box 86)
    - Original art: skirt and bag (Box 86)
    - The Performance Bible manuscript (Box 86)
    - Original art: shirt and bag (Box 212)
    - Correspondence, 2013 (Box 212)
  - Dee, Mia (Box 215)
  - Murak, Teresa (Poland) (Box 89)
    - Original art: paper made from seeds, drawings (Box 89)
    - Prints of artwork (Box 89)
  - Neagu, Paul (Romania) (Box 90-91)
    Paul Neagu's archive also includes oversize original art. See the Posters and Oversize Series, Box 130.
    - Correspondence (Box 90-91)
    - Photographs of artwork (Box 90-91, Box 214)
    - Lists of Neagu's work (Box 90-91)
    - Paul Neagu audio, May 29, 1996
      - Audio cassette 1 (Box 90-91, Audio-cassette RL01254-CS-0024, Digital-materials RL01254-SET-0002, Audio-file RL01254-CS-0024_01.wav, Audio-file RL01254-CS-0024_02.wav)
      - Audio cassette 2 (Box 90-91, Audio-cassette RL01254-CS-0025, Digital-materials RL01254-SET-0002, Audio-file RL01254-CS-0025_01.wav, Audio-file RL01254-CS-0025_02.wav)
  - Neustein, Joshua (Israel) (Box 92)
    - Midsummer Night's Dream rewrite (Box 92)
    - Correspondence, 1990s-2000s (Box 92)
    - Postcards (Box 92)
    - Photocopied articles (Box 92)
    - Correspondence, 2003 (Box 92)
    - Slides and notes (Box 92)
  - Ono, Yoko (Japan) (Box 93)
    - Correspondence, 2000-2009 (Box 93)
    - Programs for Yes Yoko Ono (Box 93)
    - Gallery advertisements (Box 93)
    - 2 buttons (Box 93)
  - Ortiz, Raphael Montañez (USA) (Box 94-97, Box 215)
    - Articles, 1962-1972 (Box 94-97)
    - Correspondence (Box 94-97)
    - Art publications (Box 94-97, Box 215)
    - Postcards and gallery cards (Box 94-97)
    - Book (Box 94-97)
    - Brochures and reports (Box 94-97)
  - Polansky, Rudolf (Austria, b. 1951) (Box 189)
    - Artists books (Box 189)
  - Saglova, Zorka (Czech Republic) (Box 173)
    - Photographs (Box 173)
    - Correspondence (Box 173)
    - Magazine and papers, including notes and information about exhibitions (Box 173)
    - 4 cassette tapes of interviews (Box 173)
    - Catalogue (Box 173)
  - Schneemann, Carolee (USA) (Box 102-106)
    - Photographs (Box 102-106)
    - Articles (Box 102-106)
    - Correspondence, 1980-2000s (Box 102-106)
    - Exhibition publications and catalogs (Box 102-106)
    - Cassette tapes (Box 102-106)
  - Schreib, Werner (Germany) (Box 175)
    - Art magazines and publications, 1960s-1970s (Box 175)
  - Schwartzkogler, Rudolf (Austria) (Box 174)
    - Correspondence with Edith Adam, 1979-1991 (Box 174)
    - Photographs (Box 174)
    - Essay by Stiles' student (Box 174)
    - Stiles' notes and articles (Box 174)
  - Seaman, Bill (USA) (Box 108)
    - Correspondence (Box 108)
    - Original art (Box 108)
    - Tenure Review booklet (Box 108)
    - "Minor Distance," audio CD with Daniel Howe, undated (Box 108, Audio-cd RL01254-CD-0001)
    - The Exquisite Mechanism of Shivers, audio CD, 1991 (Box 108, Audio-cd RL01254-CD-0002)
    - Architextural: A Hearing Aid, audio cassettes (2), undated (Box 108, Audio-cassette RL01254-CS-0009; RL01254-CS-0012)
    - Growth Curve Diagrams with Subdued Intonations / Growth Curve Diagrams for Simultaneous Receptor Motivations, audio cassette, 1980 (Box 108, Audio-cassette RL01254-CS-0010)
    - Architextural Hearing Aid / Paul and Maureen to Kris and Mark, Side 1, audio cassette, 1998 and undated (Box 108, Audio-cassette RL01254-CS-0013)
    - Otic - Info - Set / Modes for Working when not (consider Headphones), audio cassette, undated (Box 108, Audio-cassette RL01254-CS-0014)
    - Seaman Texts digital files, 1989-2004; 305 files extracted from an optical disc; approximately 130 megabytes. (Digital-materials RL01254-SET-0001, Box Digital Media Box 1)
      Mainly text-based document files (MS Word, Rich Text Format, and plain text formats), as well as a smaller number of image files (JPEG, PICT, and Adobe Photoshop formats).
    - Artintact 1, 1994; Disk image derived from a CD-ROM; approximately 320 megabytes. Original media required Mac System 7 and may not be accessible in the Rubenstein Library reading room. (Digital-materials RL01254-SET-0001, Box Digital Media Box 1)
      Includes multimedia files (Macromedia Director, AIFF audio, and CGM image formats).
  - Selz, Peter and Herschel Chipp (Box 107)
    - Photographs (Box 107)
    - Correspondence, 1976-2008 (Box 107)
    - 1982 interview by Smithsonian (Box 107)
    - Writings and articles by Stiles and others (Box 107)
    - Gallery catalog (Box 107)
  - Shapiro, Elisha (USA) (Box 109)
    - Calendars and promotion for Nihilist Industries, 1985-2004 (Box 109)
    - Bumper stickers (Box 109)
    - Correspondence (Box 109)
    - Nihilist Industries newsletters, 2012-2013 (Box 214)
  - Sharkey, John (Ireland) (Box 110)
    - Correspondence (Box 110)
    - Articles, 1980s-2000s (Box 110)
    - Discussion of DIAS, including Metzger, Ortiz, Hansen, etc. (Box 110)
    - Interview transcript (Box 110)
    - 3 audiocassettes with taped interview (Box 110)
  - Shea, Edmund, 1979-1980
    - Exhibition Photographs: "Bruce Conner's Bride", 18 photographs Exhibition photographs from Nasher exhibition, curated by Kristine Stiles (Box 209)
  - Sonfist, Alan (USA) (Box 57)
    - Correspondence, 2000s (Box 57)
    - Articles and drafts about his artwork and the environment as inspiration (Box 57)
  - Stephens, Graham (United Kingdom) (Box 110)
    - 2 catalogs (Box 110)
  - SubREAL: Dan, Calin, and Kiraly, Josif (Romania) (Box 98)
    - Original artwork (Box 98)
    - Correspondence (Box 98)
    - Promotional materials (Box 98)
  - Thompson, Mark (USA) (Box 111)
    - Correspondence (Box 111)
    - Photographs (Box 111)
    - Publications (Box 111)
    - Resource Kunst (Box 108)
    - A bone (Box 111)
    - DVD (Box 111)
    - Magnets (Box 111)
    - 3 audiocassettes with interviews (Box 111)
  - Tinguely, Jean (Switzerland) (Box 205)
    - Original work of art: collage painted handwritten letter to Stiles (Box 205)
  - Toche, Jean
    - Exhibit photographs (Box 181-187)
    - Writings, poetry, compositions, 1990s-2008 (Box 181-187)
    - Stiles/Toche materials from his exhibit, Impressions from the Rogue Bush Imperial Presidency, 2004 (Box 181-187)
    - Sketchbook of drawings Toche made following the death of his wife Virginia, 2000 (given to Stiles when completed) (Box 181-187)
    - Correspondence, 1995-2009 (Box 181-187)
    - Prints and envelopes from Toche's mail project, 2005 (Box 181-187)
    - 2 audio cassette tapes, Staten Island, 2000 (Box 181-187)
    - Of Piss @N' Pus issues, 2002-2003 (Box 181-187)
    - 13x19 prints, 2005 (Box 181-187)
    - Correspondence, 2009-2012 (Box 204)
    - Artwork, 2012 (Box 204, Box 210, Box 211)
    - Exhibition panels of multiple works, 2004 (Box 207-208)
    - Oversize photographic works (Box Tube 1-12, 14-34)
    - Correspondence, 2012-2015 (Box 211)
  - Todosijevic, Rasa (Serbia) (Box 57)
    - Correspondence, including through Marinela Kozelj, 2000s (Box 57)
    - Articles about her artwork (Box 57)
    - Gallery catalog (Box 57)
  - Tomazo, Criton (Cyprus) (Box 112)
    - Correspondence (Box 112)
    - Publications (Box 112)
    - 3 cassette tapes (Box 112)
  - Verlan, Mark (Box 85)
    - Writings (2 pages) (Box 85)
  - Viennese Actionism (Box 87-88)
    Includes artists Günter Brus, Otto Mühl, Graham Stevens, Hermann Nitsch, Valie Export.
    Oversize materials from Herman Nitsch have been removed to the Oversize Posters series. See Box 194.
    - Vienna Action Group materials (Box 87-88)
    - Graham Steven's Nothing, 1984 (Box 87-88)
    - Correspondence (Box 87-88)
    - Gallery and O.M. Theater flyers (Box 87-88)
    - Hermann Nitsch Museum flyers (Box 87-88, Box 215)
    - Original art by Günter Brus: felt collage cover Die Schanstrommel No. 7, April 1972 (Box 87-88)
    - Ausstellung Brus-Muehl-Nitsch catalog, August-September 1984 (Box 87-88)
    - Gunter Brus, Irrwisch, 1971 (Box 87-88)
      With stamp from Austrian filmmaker Kurt Kren, who exchanged it for financial support when he lived in his car in San Francisco in the early 1980s.
    - Hermann Nitsch: Das Orgien Mysterien Theater: Die Aktionen, 1962-2003, companion DVD, 2008 (Box 87, Video-disc RL01254-DVD-0004)
    - Hermann Nitsch: Island symphony, audio CD set (4 items), 1998 (Box 87, Audio-cd RL01254-CD-0003; RL01254-CD-0004; RL01254-CD-0005; RL01254-CD-0006)
  - Vostell, Wolf (Germany) (Box 113)
    - Journal (Box 113)
    - Correspondence and notes, 1970s-1980s (Box 113)
    - Gallery catalogs (Box 113)
    - Original artwork (Box 113)
    - Correspondence with Rafael, his son, 2000s (Box 113)
    - 4 audiocassettes of taped interviews, 1982-08-27 (Box 113)
      - Vostell 27 Aug 1982 Malpartida #1 (Box 113, Audio-cassette RL01254-CS-0015, Digital-materials RL01254-SET-0002, Audio-file RL01254-CS-0015_01.wav, Audio-file RL01254-CS-0015_02.wav)
      - Vostell 27 Aug 1982 Malpartida #2 (Box 113, Audio-cassette RL01254-CS-0016, Digital-materials RL01254-SET-0002, Audio-file RL01254-CS-0016_01.wav, Audio-file RL01254-CS-0016_02.wav)
      - Vostell 27 Aug 1982 #3 (Box 113, Audio-cassette RL01254-CS-0017, Digital-materials RL01254-SET-0002, Audio-file RL01254-CS-0017.wav)
    - 2 matchboxes (Box 113)
  - Waanders, Hans (Netherlands, 1955-2001) (Box 114)
    - Order: Coraciiformes-Family: Alcedinidae (Box 114)
    - Articles about the City Gallery of Contemporary Art, Raleigh, NC (Box 114)
    - Correspondence, 1990s (Box 114)
    - Kingfisher stamps, original art and prints (Box 114)
    - Standard Catalogue (artist books with inserts and Waanders' calling card) (Box 190)
    - LJsvogelwiel (Kingfisher Pond), 1989, with four original prints (made from Waanders' arm/vein) (Box 190)
    - In Search of Blue, 1988 (original art) (Box 190)
    - Bloody Tracks, 1987 (original art) (Box 190)
    - Leidabok, 1990 (original art) (Box 190)
    - Kingfishers and Queens, 1987, no. 7 (original art) (Box 190)
  - Weibel, Peter (Austria) (Box 113)
    - 3 audiocassettes, 1982-09-09 (Box 113)
      - Peter Weibel 9 Sept 1982 #1 (Box 113, Audio-cassette RL01254-CS-0018, Digital-materials RL01254-SET-0002, Audio-file RL01254-CS-0018_01.wav, Audio-file RL01254-CS-0018_02.wav)
      - Peter Weibel 9 Sept 1982 #2 (Box 113, Audio-cassette RL01254-CS-0019, Digital-materials RL01254-SET-0002, Audio-file RL01254-CS-0019_01.wav, Audio-file RL01254-CS-0019_02.wav)
      - Peter Weibel 9 Sept 1982 #3 (Box 113, Audio-cassette RL01254-CS-0020, Digital-materials RL01254-SET-0002, Audio-file RL01254-CS-0020.wav)
  - Wolff, Jamie (USA) (Box 192)
    - Twenty-two 16x20 color photographs (Box 192)
  - O'Neill, Dennis (Russia) (Box 212)
    - Correspondence, 2014 (Box 212)
    - Catalogues, retrospectives from The Moscow Studio, 1996-2000 (Box 212)
  - Popovic, Zoran (Serbia) (Box 215)
    - Trailer for "Struggle in New York," Belgrade, 2009 (DVD) (Box 215, Video-disc RL01254-DVD-0002)
    - "Worker, Printing Press Operator, Miodrag Popovic: On His Life, Work, and Free Time (31 years old, 16 years of full-time employment)," Zoran Popovic interviewed his brother Miograg-Mica May 1, 1977. DVD, 2009. (Box 215, Video-disc RL01254-DVD-0003)
    - Writings and correspondence, 2008 and undated (Box 215)
- Photographs, 7 boxes
  Photographs from Stiles' personal and academic life, including family photographs and scrapbooks, artists from around the world, DIAS photographs, and numerous unlabelled and unsorted images.
  - Artists from around the world, 1967-2004 and undated (Box 115)
    Includes Sherman Fleming (1992), Out of Actions (1998), Dan and Lia Perjovschi (1997), Romania and Ion Bitzan (1995), and Francesco Conz (1999).
  - Personal photographs (Box 115)
  - Gunter Brus, 1965-1970 (Box 115)
  - Baby book inserts, including all sorts of personal documents, 1947-1960s (2 folders) (Box 115)
  - Scrapbook of Stiles' life, 1947-1960s (birth through 1st marriage to Randolph Stiles) (Box 116)
  - High school photographs, 1961-1964 (Box 116)
  - Baby book (inserts in Box 115) (Box 116)
  - Julie Abeles photographs of Raphael Montañez Ortiz and DIAS, 1967-1968 (3 folders) (Box 117)
    Includes Hermann Nitsch, Lil Picard, and photographs of performance art by Raphael Montañez Ortiz, including animal carcasses.
  - John Prosser photographs, including DIAS, J.J. Lebel, Raphael Montañez Ortiz, 1960s-1980s (4 folders) (Box 117)
  - Raphael Montañez Ortiz and DIAS, including negatives (Box 118)
  - Rasa Todosijevic photographs of performance art, 1971-1996 (Box 118)
  - Arte Destructivo, Buenos Aires, 1961 (Box 118)
  - Geta Bratescu, Romania (Box 118)
  - Theo Allenberg (Box 118)
  - Alberto Alvin (Box 118)
  - John Prosser (Box 118)
  - Michael Broome (Box 118)
  - Out of Actions (Box 118)
  - Raphael Montañez Ortiz and DIAS photographs (Box 119)
    Photographers include Jan Van Ray, Neil B. Greenberg, Stella Waitzkin, E. Holliday, WF Dollard, and Peter Moore.
  - Viennese Action Artists (Box 119)
  - O.E. Nelson (Box 119)
  - Foto F Tas (Box 119)
  - Robin Page (Box 119)
  - Unsorted photographs, negatives, and slides (Box 171)